[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The easier and more frequently-used of the two main routes for climbing Mount Everest is the Northeast Ridge (or North Col Route).", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which European Union member is home to Santa Claus?", "correct_answer": "Finland", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyprus", "Turkey", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor played William Munny the 1992 movie Unforgiven.  William was an old  bounty hunter, who had turned into a widowed pig farmer with two kids.", "correct_answer": "Clint Eastwood", "incorrect_answers": ["Rob Campbell", "Gene Hackman", "Morgan Freeman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A character, played by which of these actors/actresses survived in the movie The Poseidon Adventure?", "correct_answer": "Red Buttons", "incorrect_answers": ["Shelly Winters", "Stella Stevens", "Gene Hackman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first person to portray James Bond in a visual medium, thus eliminating actors who voiced James Bond on radio.", "correct_answer": "Barry Nelson", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Sellers", "David Niven", "Woody Allen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Olympus Mons taller than Mt. Everest?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the wrong statement about chinchilla breeding?", "correct_answer": "Chinchillas have a 45-day gestation period.", "incorrect_answers": ["Chinchilla litters predominately consist of twins.", "Chinchillas can breed any time of the year.", "Little chinchillas are born furred and with eyes open."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character from the movie The Goonies said Here, grab the rock?", "correct_answer": "Brand", "incorrect_answers": ["Mouth", "Chunk", "Mikey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kathleen Cleary is the wife of Treasury Secretary William Cleary.  What is her nickname in the movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Kitty Kat", "incorrect_answers": ["Milk Duds", "Vroom, Vroom", "Pussycat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the cockroach when classified according to the peak of its activeness?", "correct_answer": "Nocturnal", "incorrect_answers": ["Diurnal", "None of these", "Crepuscular"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the correct atomic number of the chemical element Radon?", "correct_answer": "86", "incorrect_answers": ["85", "87", "88"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A clog is a type of shoe, made predominantly out of leather, associated with the Netherlands.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]